Guide to the Brown Brothers Harriman Records 1696-1973, 1995 (bulk, 1820-1968) MS 78
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Historical Files (1699-1974), 1820-1968; 39 Linear feet (81 document boxes, 6 oversize boxes, 12 volumes)
  - Subseries B. Subject Files (1708-1970), 31 document boxes XX OS boxes, 6 volumes
    - World War I: Financing. I, 1914-1915 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 9)
    - World War I: Financing. I, 1915-1916 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 10)
    - World War I: Financing. I, 1917 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 11)
    - World War I: Financing. II- Histoire des Finances Exterieure de la France Pendant la Guerre-excerpts and synopsis, 1914-1918 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 1)
    - World War I: Financing. II-Histoire des Finances Exterieure de la France Pendant la Guerre-excerpts and synopsis, 1914-1918 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 2)
    - World War I: Financing. II-Brown correspondence (carbons); clipping, 1914 August - 1918 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 3)
    - World War I: Financing. II-cross-reference sheets, 1914-1964 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 4)
    - World War I: Financing. II-postwar financing, 1916-1928 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 5)
    - World War I: Financing. II-correspondence of James Brown and H.P. Davison (J.P. Morgan) about French government business (originals), 1917-1920 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 6)
    - World War II, 1930-1960s (Offsite-box 61, Folder 7)
    - Zurich office, 1968 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 8)
    - Banque de France: letter from President Georges Pallain and telegram commemorating first dollar commercial export credit in syndicate form - photostats, 1915 August 25 (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 2)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: reference sheets to correspondence, 1855-1868 (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 3)
    - Collins Line: "Ocean Steamship Travel on S.S. United States and S.S. Pacific" - 1965 clipping, 1850s (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 4)
    - Foreign banks: clippings (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 5)
    - Liverpool: documents connected with public banquet, cornerstone laying for William Brown Library - photocopies, 1857 April 15 (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 6)
    - Pasque Island: deed, Daniel Wilcox to John Tucker of Dartmouth (photostats), 1696 September 29 (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 7)
    - Philadelphia office: The Philadelphia Record, April 24, 1924, 1824 (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 8)
    - Property: Wall Street deeds - originals, 1825 April 29 - 1837 March 27 (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 9)
    - Property: Wall Street deeds - originals, 1840s (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 10)
    - Property: Wall Street deeds and maps; cross-reference sheet; list of photos, 1860s - 1960s (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 11)
    - Property: Wall Street - view, map, cross-reference sheets, 1868, 1920 (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 12)
    - Property: Wall & Hanover Street Realty Co. papers; blueprint plan, 1900-1941 (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 13)
    - Property: "No. 63 Wall Street" etching by John Dix, 1928 (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 14)
    - Royal London Insurance Co. Ltd./ Liverpool and London & Globe Insurance Co. Ltd.: advertisement - printer's original, from Partners in Banking, 1837 (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 15)
    - Sun Valley: program, train route - prepress originals, 1968 (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 16)
    - Tax Department: Sarah E. Choate, 1912-1919 (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 17)
    - Tax Department: Mrs. Florence A. Pratt, 1916-1921 (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 18)
    - Tax Department: Lady Nina and Sir Mark Collet, 1917-1920 (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 19)
    - Property: sketch of downtown Manhattan from Brooklyn; photograph of lower Manhattan from Governor's Island, 1875; 1929 November 20 (Offsite-box OS 4, Folder 15)
    - Crosby Brown Collection of Musical Instruments, Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1889-1969 (Offsite-box OS 5, Folder 12)
    - Brown Brothers & Co.: correspondence about separation from Brown Shipley & Co.; partners' profit and loss statements (originals), 1918 (Offsite-box OS 6, Folder 1)
    - Martin's Bank, 1855-1962 (Offsite-box OS 6, Folder 2)
    - Property: Wall & Hanover Street Realty Co., 1890s (Offsite-box OS 6, Folder 3)
    - Tax Department: Eleanor Boardman, 1937-1939 (Offsite-box OS 6, Folder 4)
    - Liverpool: addresses at cornerstone laying for William Brown Library - glossies, 1857 April 15 (Offsite-box OS 7, Folder 1)
    - Property: abstracts from title to 63-65 Wall Street - 1960s notes, 1666-1890s (Offsite-box OS 7, Folder 2)
    - Property: deeds and maps - originals, 1830-1838 (Offsite-box OS 7, Folder 3)
    - Property: blueprint plan - 3,4,5 Hanover Street, 1919 (Offsite-box OS 7, Folder 4)
    - Property: blueprint plans for 59-61 Wall Street, 1929 (Offsite-box OS 7, Folder 5)
    - Tax Department: Charles D. Dickey, 1918-1935 (Offsite-box OS 7, Folder 6)
    - Tax Department: 4 and 5 Hanover Street - tax returns and forms, 1917-1920 (Offsite-box OS 8, Folder 1)
    - Tax Department: Sir Alexander Hargreaves Brown, Bart., 1917-1921 (Offsite-box OS 8, Folder 2)
    - Tax Department: Cornelia M. (Mrs. G. Hunter) Brown, 1919-1924 (Offsite-box OS 8, Folder 3)
    - Boston office: receipt book, 1847-1875 (Offsite-box BBH-2, Volume 7)
    - Boston office: notebook, 1930s (Offsite-box BBH-2, Volume 8)
    - Property: Wall & Hanover Street Realty Co. - stockholders record, 1900 (Offsite-box BBH-2, Volume 9)
    - Property: Wall & Hanover Street Realty Co. - stockholders record, 1910-1928 (Offsite-box BBH-2, Volume 10)
    - Syndicates Department: notebook, 1900-1911 (Offsite-box BBH-2, Volume 11)
    - West Virginia Debt Settlement: press copies of correspondence, 1898-1912 (Offsite-box BBH-2, Volume 12)
  - Subseries C. People Files (pre-1600s -1973), 7.3 Linear feet 17 document boxes
    The subseries includes original and photocopied material specific to former and current (as of 1968) employees, partners, clients, as well as genealogical information about various branches of the Brown and related families. A large amount of the information, especially that to do with Brown family members and partners, consists of cross-reference sheets pointing to items in other subseries of the Historical Files.
    Some folders in Subseries C.i. had written on them the subject's lines of descent from Brown partners. These have been photocopied onto acid-free paper.
    Among the clients in Subseries C.iii. are nobleman Otto of Hapsburg; playwright Philip Barry and his wife Ellen; poet Archibald Macleish at the time he served as Librarian of Congress; and humorist Dorothy Parker and her husband Alan Campbell, whose records include 1938 ticket stubs they claimed as deductible expenses. These materials may have come from Tax Department employee Catherine Barrett's scrapbooks, which are included in Series VI. Scrapbooks and Collected Materials.
    Among the former employees in Subseries C.iv. who worked briefly for the firm were the son of New York diarist Philip Hone; and Edward Heath, who later served as England's Prime Minister.
    There is some duplication of information about Brown family members in Subseries C.v. and vi., but most information on family members who were partners in the firm is included in the latter subseries. Materials include cross-reference sheets, genealogical information, clippings, photographs and other images, and information submitted by living current and retired partners in response to requests from Kouwenhoven.
    Subseries C.vi. provides information on non-business aspects of the partners' lives and interests, including William Brown's donations in his home town of Liverpool, England; John Crosby Brown and William Adams Brown's involvement with Union Theological Seminary in New York City; and the extensive international political careers of W. Averell Harriman, Robert A. Lovett, and Robert V. Roosa.
    Sarah B. Brown, who was John Crosby Brown's great-granddaughter, donated a significant amount of the material in her great-grandfather's files, including photographs and letters from his son James Brown to his wife Mary Elizabeth Adams Brown from France in 1917, where he was working for the American Red Cross. Subseries C.v. and vi. also document Mrs. Brown's research travels in support of material relevant to the Historical Files.
    The People files are arranged in their original six subsubseries
    i. Genealogy ii. Various People iii. Famous clients iv. Employees: current and former v. Brown family vi. Partners
    Three account books from the commercial credit department have been removed from partner Ellery James Sedgewick's file and included with the oversize materials at the end of the series. Glass negatives from Montague Collet and John Crosby Brown's records have been rehoused in Series VIII. Visual Materials.
    The subseries is arranged in its original six components:
    Missing Title
    Subseries i. Genealogy
    Subseries ii. Various people
    Subseries iii. Famous clients
    Subseries iv. Employees: current and former
    Subseries v. Brown family
    Subseries vi. Partners
    Three account books from the commercial credit department have been removed from partner Ellery Sedgwick James's file and included with the oversize materials at the end of the series.
    Glass negatives from Montagu Collet's and John Crosby Brown's records have been rehoused in Subseries VIII.A. Assorted Visual Materials.
    Delano, William Adams, 1874-1960; Harriman family; Roosa, Robert V.; Parker, Dorothy, 1893-1967; Magoun (Family); MacLeish, Archibald, 1892-1982; Lovett, Robert A. (Robert Abercrombie), 1895-1986; Bush, Prescott Sheldon, 1895-1972; Brown, William, Sir, 1784-1864; Brown, William Adams, 1865-1943; Brown, Thatcher Magoun, 1876-1954; Brown, Mary Elizabeth, 1842-1918; Brown, John Crosby, 1838-1909; Brown, James, 1863-1943; Brown, Alexander, 1764-1834; Barry, Philip, 1896-1949; Adams, William, 1807-1880; Harriman, W. Averell (William Averell), 1891-1986; Harriman, Edward Henry, 1848-1909
    - Subseries C.i. Genealogy (1700s-1960s), 6 folders
      - Brown family information: Muncasters, Stewart Brown, 1800s-1968 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 1)
      - Descendants of William Brown: genealogy lent by Abbott Harmon Brown - photocopy, 1700s-1900s (Offsite-box 62, Folder 2)
      - Descendants of William Brown: genealogy lent by Abbott Harmon Brown - photocopy, 1700s-1900s (Offsite-box 62, Folder 3)
      - Brown family tree; ancestry of Alexander Brown, 1800s (Offsite-box 62, Folder 4)
      - Delano family, 1860s-1960s (Offsite-box 62, Folder 5)
      - Gerry/ Neilson/ Harriman families, 1800s (Offsite-box 62, Folder 6)
      - Gerry/ Neilson family trees, 1800s-1900s (Offsite-box OS 7, Folder 7)
    - Subseries C.ii. Various People (1933-1969), 1 folder
      - Correspondence and inquiries, 1933-1969 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 7)
    - Subseries C.iii. Famous Clients (1931-1966), 4 folders
      - Philip and Ellen S. Barry, 1931-1938 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 8)
      - Brown-MacLeish, 1936-1966 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 9)
      - Dorothy Parker and Alan Campbell, 1931-1965 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 10)
      - Ridgeway, Robinson (formerly Blumenthal), Thompson, 1943-1965 (Offsite-box 62, Folder 11)
    - Subseries C.iv. Employees: Current and Former (1840s - 1973), 5 folders
      - Alumni: profiles and information, Bell-Wilson, 1840s-1973 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 1)
      - Alumni: memos and correspondence, 1965 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 2)
      - Current employees: cross-reference sheets and announcements, A-Z, 1952-1967 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 3)
      - Former employees: cross-reference sheets and announcements, A-L, 1832-1964 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 4)
      - Former employees: cross-reference sheets and announcements, M-Z, 1867-1965 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 5)
    - Subseries C.v. Brown Family (1600s-1970), 7 folders
      - Photographs, 1886-1970 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 6)
      - Cross-reference sheets, 1895-1950 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 7)
      - James Crosby Brown, William Adams Brown, Sir William Richmond Brown, Winthrop Gilman Brown, 1888-1965 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 8)
      - George Alexander Brown, Gordon Hargreaves Brown, Agnes Hewlett Brown, J. Monroe Hewlett, Amy B. DeForest, William Adams Delano, 1863-1960 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 9)
      - F.J.F. Edlmann, William F. Halsey, William H. Hands, John Knox, David N. Lord, Joseph C. Lucey, Moore family, 1870-1964 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 10)
      - Magoun family, James B. Markoe, Arthur L. Nash, Harmon Browns, 1600-1933 (Offsite-box 63, Folder 11)
      - Emily de Forest White, living descendants in 1916, Hewett family tree, Brown coat of arms, Gihon family, 1860-1967 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 1)
    - Subseries C.vi. Partners (pre-1600s - 1970), 5.3 Linear feet 12.5 boxes
      Names are arranged alphabetically either individually or grouped together in one folder. Partners' names are listed with their birth and death dates as noted on the original folders: those corrected or added in processing are shown in brackets.
      Various oversize photographic portraits of partners were found organized separately in the Records. Although originally marked as belonging to the Subject files, they have been included in this subseries for consistency. The Herman Hoskier portrait was unidentified but is labeled from the same photographic studio as others found in the group and matches an image of him found in John Crosby Brown's One Hundred Years of Merchant Banking.
      An audio tape from W. Averell Harriman's files has been removed to Subseries VIII.C. Audio tapes.
      Brown, John Crosby, 1838-1909; Brown, James, 1863-1943; Brown, Mary Elizabeth, 1842-1918; Roosa, Robert V.; Lovett, Robert A. (Robert Abercrombie), 1895-1986; Harriman, W. Averell (William Averell), 1891-1986; Harriman, Edward Henry, 1848-1909; Bush, Prescott Sheldon, 1895-1972; Brown, William, Sir, 1784-1864; Brown, Thatcher Magoun, 1876-1954
      - List of partners, prepared for Partners in Banking, 1968 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 2)
      - David Ackerman (1895-1968), 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 3)
      - Reverend William Adams (1807-1881), 1870-1880 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 4)
      - James Adger (1777-1858), 1818-1966 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 5)
      - Joseph Eugene Banks (1908-[2000] ), 1948-1969 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 6)
      - William Ezra Bowen (1797-1866), 1837-1861 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 7)
      - Alexander Brown (1764-1834), Mrs. Alexander Brown (Grace Davison, 1758-1843), pre-1800s-1830s (Offsite-box 64, Folder 8)
      - Alexander Brown (1858-1949), 1863-1924 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 9)
      - Sir Alexander Hargreaves Brown, Bt. (1844-1922), 1846-1922 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 10)
      - Clarence Stewart Brown (1840-1875), 1866-1868 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 11)
      - Edward Clifton Brown (1870-1944), 1897-1933 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 12)
      - George Brown (1787-1859), 1837-1857 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 13)
      - George Alexander Brown (1803- 1865): diary and memoir - photocopies with annotations, 1852-1865 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 14)
      - George Alexander Brown (1803- 1865): diary and memoir - photocopies with annotations, 1852-1865 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 15)
      - George Alexander Brown (1803- 1865): image, 1860s (Offsite-box 64, Folder 16)
      - George Hunter Brown (1835-1900), 1859-1900 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 1)
      - James Brown (1791-1877), 1825-1845 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 2)
      - James Brown (1791-1877): images, 1844 - c. 1868 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 3)
      - James Brown (1791-1877), 1848-1861 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 4)
      - James Brown (1791-1877), 1862-1876 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 5)
      - James Brown (1791-1877): obituaries (Offsite-box 65, Folder 6)
      - James Brown (1791-1877), 1880-1948 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 7)
      - James Brown (1863-1935), 1864-1914 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 8)
      - James Brown (1863-1935), 1915-1929 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 9)
      - James Brown (1863-1935): personal and business correspondence, 1918-1925 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 10)
      - James Brown (1863-1935), 1933-1935 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 11)
      - James Crosby Brown (1872-1930), 1897-1964 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 12)
      - James Crosby Brown (1872-1930): Mrs. Brown's checkbooks and checks, 1909, 1920 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 13)
      - James Crosby Brown (1872-1930): letters to wife Agnes Hewlett Brown from American Red Cross, Paris, 1917 August 12 - November (Offsite-box 66, Folder 1)
      - James Crosby Brown (1872-1930): Red Cross correspondence, 1917 September - 1918 February (Offsite-box 66, Folder 2)
      - James Crosby Brown (1872-1930): telegrams and drafts about his illness, 1917 November - 1918 January (Offsite-box 66, Folder 3)
      - James Crosby Brown (1872-1930): letters to wife Agnes Hewlett Brown, 1917 December - 1918 January (Offsite-box 66, Folder 4)
      - James Crosby Brown (1872-1930): letters to his mother Mary E. Adams Brown, 1918 January - February (Offsite-box 66, Folder 5)
      - James Crosby Brown (1872-1930): estate of Mary E. Adams Brown, 1921-1927 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 6)
      - James Muncaster Brown (1820-1890), 1844-1888 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 7)
      - James Muncaster Brown (1820-1890), 1889-1904 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 8)
      - John A. Brown (1788-1872), 1818-1942 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 9)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909), pre-1600s - 1870 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 10)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): wife Mary E. Adams Brown's journal of a trip to Europe, 1860 June - November (Offsite-box 66, Folder 11)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): index to letterbook, sent mainly from Liverpool, 1861 February - 1869 March (Offsite-box 66, Folder 12)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): journal of wedding trip, 1864 December 14 - 1865 September 6 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 1)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909), 1873-1886 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 2)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): wife Mary E. Adams Brown journals - 1873 California trip; 1874, 1877 southern trips, 1873, 1874, 1877 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 3)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): cross-reference sheets, 1880-1906 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 4)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): wife Mary E. Adams Brown's diary, extract, photo, 1881-1883 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 5)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): letters from wife Mary E. Adams Brown to her son James Crosby Brown (1 of 4), 1881 June 5 - 1898 April 6 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 6)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): letters from wife Mary E. Adams Brown to her son James Crosby Brown (2 of 4), 1881 June 5 - 1898 April 6 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 7)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): letters from wife Mary E. Adams Brown to her son James Crosby Brown (3 of 4), 1881 June 5 - 1898 April 6 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 8)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): letters from wife Mary E. Adams Brown to her son James Crosby Brown (4 of 4), 1881 June 5 - 1898 April 6 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 9)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): at Pasque Island, bedroom at Brighthurst - images, 1881, 1890 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 1)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): wife Mary E. Adams Brown's diaries of Russian and Mexican trips, 1882 February, 1886 February - March (Offsite-box 68, Folder 2)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): "Brighthurst Visiting Book No. 1" - images, 1888 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 3)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): home, 36 East 37th street - images, 1880s (Offsite-box 68, Folder 4)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): home "Brighthurst", Orange, New Jersey - images, 1880s (Offsite-box 68, Folder 5)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): background research, 1892-1899 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 6)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): cross-reference sheets, 1900-1965 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 7)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): photo, portrait, grandchildren - images, 1902, 1908, 1912 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 8)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): letter, Sunday prayers, 1906, 1907 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 9)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): will, disposition of estate, 1906, 1907 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 10)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): with granddaughters May and Emily - images, c. 1907 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 11)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): account of last weeks, sayings, by son William Adams Brown, 1909 May 16 - June 25 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 12)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): honorary and memorial minutes - Union Theological Seminary, U. S. Trust, Presbyterian Church, Metropolitan Museum, 1909 May - October (Offsite-box 68, Folder 13)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): funeral services, Brighthurst, Madison Square Presbyterian Church, 1909 June 28, 29 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 14)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): obituaries and biographies, 1909 June 29 - 1940 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 15)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): Memorial services Union Theological Seminary, Madison Square Church, 1909 November (Offsite-box 68, Folder 16)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): dedication of St. Cloud memorial Sunday school building, 1909-1910 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 17)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): account of executors, estate tax, 1910 October, 1911 May (Offsite-box 68, Folder 18)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): Clifton Chapel gift, dedication of tower at Union Theological Seminary, 1915, 1928 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 1)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): wife Mary E. Adams Brown charitable donations ("Subscriptions"), 1917 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 2)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): death and obituaries of wife Mary E. Adams Brown, 1918 February - September (Offsite-box 69, Folder 3)
      - John Crosby Brown (1838-1909): wife Mary E. Adams Brown will; estate settlement; Candace Wheeler connection, 1918, 1924 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 4)
      - Moreau D. Brown (1905 - [1974]), 1912-1969 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 5)
      - Stewart Brown (1802-1880), 1825-1880 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 6)
      - Stewart Brown (1802-1880): receipts, letters to and from executors, 1881-1884 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 7)
      - Stewart Henry Brown (1831-1905), 1846-1905 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 8)
      - Thatcher Magoun Brown (1876-1954): cross-reference sheets, images, 1885-1920 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 9)
      - Thatcher Magoun Brown (1876-1954): letters to parents from Lawrenceville School and Yale University - originals, 1886-1893 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 10)
      - Thatcher Magoun Brown (1876-1954): letters to and from his parents about Yale, Europe, smoking - originals, 1894-1897, 1900 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 11)
      - Thatcher Magoun Brown (1876-1954): letters to his parents - transcripts, 1895-1900 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 12)
      - Thatcher Magoun Brown (1876-1954): letters from London to wife Caro Noyes Brown - originals, 1907-1908 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 13)
      - Thatcher Magoun Brown (1876-1954): letters to wife Caro Noyes Brown - transcripts, 1908 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 14)
      - Thatcher Magoun Brown (1876-1954): cross-reference sheets, images, 1912-1951 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 15)
      - Thatcher Magoun Brown (1876-1954): personal letters, World War I - originals and carbons, 1914-1918 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 16)
      - Thatcher Magoun Brown (1876-1954): letters to wife Caro Noyes Brown from trip to Sweden: originals and transcripts; 1966 correspondence, 1918-1919 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 17)
      - Thatcher Magoun Brown (1876-1954): work for Yale Alumni Fund, Placement Service, 1921, 1922, 1944 (Offsite-box 69, Box 18)
      - Thatcher Magoun Brown (1876-1954): cross-reference sheets, images, 1925-1938 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 1)
      - Thatcher Magoun Brown (1876-1954): correspondence received, 1933, 1948, 1949 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 2)
      - Thatcher Magoun Brown (1876-1954): 50th anniversary with Brown Brothers Harriman, 1947 October (Offsite-box 70, Folder 3)